AoM Records 5593
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series D. Committee Records
    - Committee on the Status of Women in the Management Profession, 1973-1975 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      Report and Correspondence
    - Constitution Committee, 1961-1967 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, Proposed Constitution, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Constitution Committee, 1967-1972 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Constitution Committee Recommended Changes (Box 64, Folder 18)
      no date
    - Constitution Committee Recommended Changes (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Editorial Search Committee (for editor of A.M. Journal), 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Editors, Associate - Academy of Management Journal and Review, Selection Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Editors, Associate - Academy of Management Journal and Review, Selection Committee, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Election Committee, Biographical Sketches and Tabulated Results (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Election Committee, Biographic and Election Results, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Election Committee, Election of Officers, Material, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Election Committee, Nominations and Results of Elections, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Election of Officers, Ballot and Biographies, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Election Committee, Officers and Committees, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - European, Japanese Seminars, 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - European, Japanese Seminars, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee, 1961-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Institute for Administrative Research, Inc, 1966-1970 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      Research and publication agency of AM
    - Institute for Administrative Research, 1971-1974 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      program for operation
    - Institute for Administrative Research (Box 66, Folder 4)
      Descriptive Pamphlet, undated
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      Includes 5 year plan for the Academy of Management, opinion survey, establish divisions, changes in constitution
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Management Education and Development Committee, 1962-1969 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      Proposal for field survey
    - Management Education and Development Committee, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      Report to AM
    - Management Education Committee, Questionnaire, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Management Education and Development Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      Report of Survey on Management Education Curriculum at Various Universities
    - Management History Committee, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Management History Committee, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      Report
    - Management History Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Management Values and Styles Committee, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Membership and Public Relations Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Membership and Public Relations Committee, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Membership Director Selection Committee, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Membership (Box 67, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, pre-1950
    - Membership Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      Correspondence on Formation of and Officer Selection
    - Membership, 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Membership, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
    - Membership, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 6-8)
    - Membership, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 9-10)
    - Membership, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 11-12)
    - Membership, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Membership, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Membership, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Membership, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 16-23)
    - Membership, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Membership, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Membership, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Membership List, 1950 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Membership List, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      includes Invitations, Acceptances, Refusals
    - Membership List, Roster of Members, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Membership List, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Membership List, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Membership List, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Membership List, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      Includes New Members
    - Membership List, New Members, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Membership List, New Members, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Membership List, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Membership List, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 11-12)
    - Membership List, New Members, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Membership List, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Membership List, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Membership List, # 1-3, New Members, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Membership List, Officers of the Academy, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Membership List, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Membership List, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Membership List, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Membership List, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 21-25)
    - Membership List, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 26-29)
    - Membership List, List of Executive Board, Governors, Committee Chairman, 1971-1973 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Membership List, New Members, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Membership Lists Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Membership List, Directory, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Membership List, Directory, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Membership List, Directory, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Membership List, Directory, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Membership List, Directory, 1975-1976 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Membership List, Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Membership List, Directory, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Membership List, Directory, 1984-1986 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Membership, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Membership List (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Membership, Roster of Members, 1948 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      20-Apr-48
    - Membership Committee, Roster of Members, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      1-Jan-52
    - Membership Committee, Roster of Members and Acceptance Letters, 1954 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      1-Sep-54
    - Membership Committee, Roster of Members, 1954 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      27-Dec-54
    - Membership Committee, Annual Membership Report, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Membership Committee, Roster, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Membership Roster, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Membership, Criteria for Executive Membership by G. J. Gore, Vice President, Membership (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Membership Committee, Membership Data (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Membership Applications Blanks (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Membership, Applications (Box 70, Folder 2)
      includes "Procedure for Processing Applications for Membership"
    - Membership, Applications (Box 70, Folder 3)
      includes form letter indicating approval of application
    - Membership, Applications, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 4-5)
    - Membership, Applications, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 6-7)
    - Membership, Applications, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Membership, Applications, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Membership, Applications (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Membership, Brochure for New Members, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 11-12)
    - Membership, Dues: Correspondence and Records, 1952-1961 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Membership, Dues: Correspondence and Records, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Membership, Dues: Correspondence and Records, 1960-1962 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Membership, Dues: Correspondence and Records, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Membership, Dues: Correspondence and Records, 1963-1971 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Membership, Welcome Letters, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 18-19)
    - Membership, General (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Membership List and Correspondence, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Membership List and New Members, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Membership List and New Members, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Membership, General "The Research Interests and Activities of the Academy's Membership", 1967 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Membership, Annual Report, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      9/71 - 12/71
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      Jan-72
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      1/72 - 2/72
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      2/72 - 4/72
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      4/72 - 6/72
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      6/72 - 8/72
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      9/72 - 12/72
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      1/73 - 4/73
    - Membership, Correspondence of Vice President of Membership, George Gore, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      4/73 - 8/73
    - Membership, Requests for Mailing Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Membership, General, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      includes "The Development of the Membership Function," Membership Reports, etc.
    - Membership, General (Box 71, Folder 13-14)
    - Membership, Areas of Special Competence (for members) (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Membership, Computer Listing, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Membership, Application and Brochures (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Membership Characteristics Survey, Span Date (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, Executive Officers, 1953-1959 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1959-1967 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Nominations Committee, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 9-19)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Nominations Committee, Ballot for Officer Election, 1979-1980 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Nominations Committee, Results of 1978-79 AOM Elections, 1978-1979 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Placement Committee, Acad Positions, 1962-1969 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Placement Committee, Forms and Correspondence, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Placement Committee, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Placement, Committee on Academic, Report, 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Placement Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Placement Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Placement Committee, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Placement Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Placement Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Placement Committee, Rosters of Applicants, Academic Openings, 1967-1969 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Placement Committee, Rosters of Applicants, Academic Openings, 1970-1972 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Placement Committee, Placement Rosters, Pamphlets, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Placement Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Placement Committee, Placement Rosters, 1974-1979 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Placement Committee, Placement Rosters, 1980-1983 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Placement Committee, Placement Rosters, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Placement Committee, Applicant Forms and Job Position Forms, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Placement Committee, Placement Service Description (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Proceedings Editor Selection Committee, William Glueck, Chair, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings Editor Selection Committee, William Glueck, Chair, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings Editor Selection Committee, William Glueck, Chair, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of the Academy of Management, Editor Selection Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Professional Division Policy Committee Meeting, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      Agenda and Minutes, October 1977
    - Public Relations Committee, Brochure, 1954-1969 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Publications Planning Committee, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Publications Planning Committee, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Publications Committee, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Publicity Committee, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Research and Publications Committee, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 13)
      Research Bulletin
    - Research and Publications Committee, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      Correspondence and Special Announcements
    - Research and Publications Committee, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      Research Grants
    - Research Committee, 1949-1963 (Box 74, Folder 16)
      Grants--funded and awarded by Academy
    - Research Committee, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 17)
      Report on Courses Recommended for Inclusion of a Department of Management
    - Research Committee, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 18)
      Special Announcements
    - Research Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Research Committee, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 20)
      includes "The Research Interests and Activities of the Academy's Membership, a report by the committee
    - Research Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Research Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 22-23)
    - Research Committee (Box 74, Folder 24)
      Special Announcements, Reports, etc., undated
    - Scholarship Awards Committee, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Scholarship Awards Committee (Box 74, Folder 26)
      Committee, Preliminary Report on Scholarship Award, undated
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon (Student Division), 1964 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      includes Constitution
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon (Student Division), 1964 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon, 1964-1967 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon, 1967-1969 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      Includes Newsletter
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon, 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon, 1970-1973 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      Guidelines on Admin; Striation
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon (Box 75, Folder 8)
      Includes pamphlets, booklets and copies of "The Manager's Key," Journal of SIE
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Sigma Iota Epsilon, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      Newsletter, Fall 1978
    - Site and Date Selection Committee, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      Includes correspondence pertaining to selection of location for annual meeting
    - Site and Date Selection Committee, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Site and Date Selection Committee, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Site and Date Selection Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Site Selection Committee, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 15)
      Correspondence of Powell Niland, Chairman, Selection for '83
    - Site Selection Committee, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 16)
      Report, Fall 1978
    - Site Committee, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 17)
      Letter of Acceptances and Memorandum, September, 1978
    - Site Selection Committee, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 18)
      Report on Survey of Members' Preference for Annual Meeting Arrangements, July 7, 1979
    - Site and Date Selection Committee, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Social Policy Research and Action Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 75, Folder 20)
      Set up Workshop at 1971 annual meeting
    - Special Projects Committee, 1965-1972 (Box 75, Folder 21)
      Set up Research Institute, Report on: Hiring administration v. voluntary leadership of Academy
    - Standing Committees (Box 75, Folder 22)
      Consists of a list of committees and members interested in those committees, undated
    - Task Force and Professional Division Policy Committee, Task Force Report Draft, 1978-1979 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - U. S. Seminars Committee (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Committee Assignments, 1966 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Committees, General, 1949-1972 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Committees, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 27)
      Consists of correspondence pertaining to the functions and purposes of Academy committees
  - Sub-Series E. Regional Division Records
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Second Annual Meeting, Philadelphia, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Third Annual Meeting, College Park, MD, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Fourth Annual Meeting, Cambridge, MA, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Fifth Annual Meeting, New York City, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Sixth Annual Meeting, Washington, DC, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Seventh Annual Meeting, Amherst, MA, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Meeting, "Management Research and Practice," edited by M. William Frey, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Eighth Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, VA, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Regional Division, Fin. Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Regional Division, Minutes and Secretaries Report, 1978-1982 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, 18th Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 16)
      Includes vouchers
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Regional Division, Minutes of Board Meeting, Baltimore, MD, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 17)
      May-82
    - Eastern Academy of Management, General, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 18)
      Includes paper: "Behavioral Science Applications to Management: An Appraisal" by Alan C. Filley
    - Eastern Academy of Management, General (Box 76, Folder 19)
      incudes Constitution
    - Eastern Academy of Management, 15th Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 20)
      May 11-13, 1978
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Membership Mailing Lists (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Proceedings, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Proceedings, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Proceedings, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Academy of Management, Proceedings, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Midwest Division, The Annual Meeting, Ohio State University, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Midwest Division, Seventh Annual Meeting, Madison, WI, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Midwest Division, Ninth Annual Meeting, Lexington, KY, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Midwest Regional Division, Academy, Meeting Program, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      April 8 - 9, 1966
    - Midwest Division, Tenth Annual Meeting, Illinois, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Midwest Division, Eleventh Annual Meeting, St. Louis, MO, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Midwest Division, Twelfth Annual Meeting, Bloomington, IN, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Midwest Division, Thirteenth Annual Meeting, East Lansing, MI, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Midwest Division, Fourteenth Annual Meeting, Cleveland, OH, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Midwest Division, Fifteenth Annual Conference, Program, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      Apr-72
    - Midwest Division, 24th Annual Conference, Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Midwest Division, Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Midwest Division, Proceedings of the 13th Annual Meeting, "Management and the 70's: Problems, Perspectives and Possibilities", 1970 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Midwest Division, Proceedings of the 14th Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Midwest Division, Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Midwest Division, Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Midwest Meeting, Correspondence and Reports, Cleveland, OH, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Midwest Division, Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Midwest Division, 23rd Annual Conference, Cincinnati, OH, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Midwest Division, 23rd Annual Conference, Cincinnati, OH, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      Proceedings
    - Midwest Division, General (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Midwest Division, General (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Mountain-Plains Management Conference Proceedings, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      October 16-18, 1975
    - Southern Division, Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Southern Division, Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Southern Division, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Southern Division, Annual Meeting, Roanoke, VA, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Southern Division, Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Southern Division, Annual Meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Southern Division, Annual Meeting, Washington, DC, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Southern Division, Annual Meeting, St. Louis, MO, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Southern Division, Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Southern Division, Annual Meeting, Miami Beach, FL, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Southern Division, Proceedings of Annual Meeting (Box 80, Folder 11)
      197?
    - Southern Division, General (Box 80, Folder 12)
      Includes Policy Statements, Constitution, etc.
    - Southern Division, General (Box 80, Folder 13)
      Includes Membership Lists
    - Southern Division, General (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Southern Management Association, Proceedings, 1982-1984 (Box 80, Folder 15-16)
    - Southern Management Association, Miscellaneous Publications, etc., 1967-1980 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Southwest Division, Minutes, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Management Association, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Southwest Division, Business Meeting Minutes, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Southwest Division, Business Meeting Minutes, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Southwest Division, Executive Committee Meeting, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      May-65
    - Southwest Division, Annual Meeting, Program and Materials, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      April 7 - 9, 1966
    - Southwest Division, Eighth Annual Meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Southwest Division Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Southwest Division, Business Meeting Minutes, 1964-1969 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Southwest Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, Miscellaneous Papers, 1965-1967 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Southwest Business Meeting Minutes, 1970-1978 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Southwest Division, Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Southwest Division, Mailing List, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Southwest Division, Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Southwest Division, 12th, 13th Annual Meetings, Dallas, TX, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Southwest Division, 14th Annual Meeting, San Antonio, TX, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Southwest Division, 15th Annual Meeting, Dallas, TX, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Southwest Division, Minutes, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      Mar-79